Finding Aid for David E. Davis papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Film
  - Deadline Now #193, "The Big Three's topsy-turvy world," Guests: Sean McAlinden and David E. Davis, Jr., WGTE Public Media, June 12, 2009, DVD (Box 22)